typewith.me 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy - LockerGnome

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy. 

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. 
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. 
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. 
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. 
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date. 
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. 
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. 

##  Third Party Advertisers  

This site recently updated its advertising base to include third party advertisers that might include:

**North America: Ad servers**

**North America: Rich media**

  * 

**North America: Research**

This website uses cookies that allow advertisers to serve ads to its visitors across various ad networks. All data that is collected by the cookies cannot uniquely identify the website visitor, rather, it collects non personalized information based on likes, interests and website usage data, this allows advertisers to serve ads to them as they browse other websites across the internet. To opt out of the ad networks, website visitors are encouraged to go here: [Google Ad Network Opt Out](http://www.google.com/settings/ads?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCjMUi-PFaWXqIeOJnrItWrijpjPJTpDWiXRU3gWpVkxI2a9zeYyZDMNT0wJdiNh15QY4LPa7OVwcL6ylHzBp9WAz9kboA) or by using the [NAI OPT OUT TOOL](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). 

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. 

Lockergnome Inc.  
1420 NW Gilman Blvd #2543  
Issaquah, WA 98027
